it can easily be mistaken for other coral
species name
fire basket burning pain as it can
cause on touch this depends on It
small harpoon like structures so
called knidos sews in
fire basket skeleton injecting a
toxic substance in Alten touches
fire baskets everything from stones to
plastic items and are often found in Varma
shallow water around coral reef divers
are at greatest risk of coming into contact
with
fire basket or found near other popular ones
dive sites if you come into contact with
fire baskets wash the wound with sea water
and seek medical advice about it
needed as a diver Maybe you are afraid of